You're a pro at JavaScript,
إنكم محترفون في JavaScript،
but that does not mean you can just "kick back and coast."
ولكن ذلك لا يعني أنه يمكنكم فقط "الاستهانة بالأمر والاسترخاء".
These new additions in ES6 have brought a major change to the language.
فلقد قامت هذه الإضافات الجديدة في ES6 بإدخال تغيير رئيسي على اللغة.
You can not just ignore them in bank on
ولا يمكنكم تجاهلها اعتمادًا على
your existing knowledge of a now behind-the-times technology.
معرفتكم الحالية بالتكنولوجيا المتأخرة حاليًا.
You have got to get up, dig into the features,
فيجب أن تنهضوا وتبحثوا في الميزات
read the specification, follow some tutorials,
وتقرؤوا المواصفات وتتابعوا بعض البرامج التعليمية
maybe even write some of your own.
وربما حتى تكتبون بعضها بأنفسكم.
The Web is an evolving platform and you need to evolve with it.
الويب هو نظام أساسي يتطور بمرور الوقت وعليكم التطور معه.
Imagine being stuck on old horrible equipment when
تخيلوا أنكم متعلقون بمعدات قديمة وشنيعة في حين أن
there are newer nicer tools available for you to use.
هناك أدوات أحدث وأجمل منها متوفرة لكم لاستخدامها.
You now know how JavaScript language improvements are
تعرفون الآن كيف يتم إجراء تحسينات على لغة JavaScript
made and where to find browser support for them.
وأين يمكنكم العثور على دعم المستعرض الخاص بها.
You have got the tools. You just need to use them.
لقد حصلتم على الأدوات. وتحتاجون فقط إلى استخدامها.